Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/mohsen-ghafari (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

PBR Authoring Autodesk Maya Autodesk 3ds Max

Languages

Persian (Native or Bilingual) English (Full Professional)

Mohsen Ghafari

3D Environment Artist in VR/AR Reality Labs @ Meta San Francisco Bay Area

Summary

I'm very passionate in Designing 3D Environment Art for Games. I bring 'Environment Art' experience in the field by developing art and assets for both architecture and organic environments. I have handson experience in using Maya and 3ds Max for modeling, Zbrush for sculpting, and substance painter for texturing plus unreal engine for lighting, rendering, and post-production. I also am capable of making modular assets for a bigger environment and using trim sheets and unique textures to make a wide variety of assets for games.

Experience

Meta

3D Environment Artist (Insight Global) November 2021 - Present (1 year 6 months) Burlingame, California, United States

High Moon Studios Associate Environment Artist November 2020 - November 2021 (1 year 1 month) San Francisco Bay Area

- Utilized the Engine to Environment Art from Blockout to Final Polished art Quality
- Working closely with Game Designer team to ensure the quality of gameplay
- Actively participate in teamwork within Art team to have the consistent and functional look dev from Alpha to beta polish and ship the high quality look playable map
- Worked on Nakatomi building in "Call of Duty Warzone" seasonal chapter
- worked on Village and logging Area in "Call of Duty Warzone Pacific"

Centre for Creative Content and Digital Innovation, University of Malaya

Research Assistant

April 2014 - April 2015 (1 year 1 month)

Level 7, Chancellery Building, University of Malaya (UM), KL, MY

Fireworks Solutions International Design Internship February 2013 - May 2013 (4 months)

Digital Ads Design, Web Design

Education

Academy of Art University

Master of Fine Arts (MFA), Game Development · (2015 - 2018)

Multimedia University
Bachelor of Multimedia (Honours), Multimedia Advertising
Design · (2010 - 2014)